(Alice:)- Call me.
- Sorry, palm's a little sweaty.
(Leonard:)What's that word?
(Hot girl:)- Alice.
- Oh, right, your name.
That makes more sense than "penis."
(Alice:)Later.
(Howard:)Did we just see you pick up a girl
in a comic book store?
Because if you did, you get your picture
up there on the Wall of Heroes.
(Leonard:)No, I don't think I picked her up.
Besides, I have a girIfriend.
(Stuart:)Doesn't matter.
This is the closest anyone's ever come.
(Stuart:)You're going on the wall, my friend.
(Sheldon:)Be sure to check the mail.
(Leonard:)How many times are you gonna tell me?
What's with you?
(Sheldon:)Nothing.
It's not suspicious that I'm fixating.
(Sheldon:)It's consistent with my personality.
(Sheldon:)- Right.
- Hey, guys.
(Leonard:)More Halloween candy? Didn't you just
buy a bunch of it yesterday?
(Penny:)Oh, yeah, that's gone.
(Penny:)It's a rough month when Halloween
and PMS hit at the same time.